{"data":[{"question":"Cleaners in big cities usually get ___ by the hour.","a":"paying","b":"pay","c":"to pay","d":"paid","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Get + past participle = be + past participle \n- To make passive structures in informal spoken English, we sometime use get instead of be with the past participle","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Only one of those best sellers is ___.","a":"worth being read","b":"worth to read","c":"worth reading","d":"worth of reading","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Be worth verb_ing: used to say that something is interesting, useful, or helpful","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"What do you think of the computer game?\" \"Oh, great. It's worth ___ a second time.\"","a":"to be played","b":"to play","c":"being played","d":"playing","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Be worth verb_ing: used to say that something is interesting, useful, or helpful","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"These volunteers asked ___ to work in a poor foreign country.","a":"to send","b":"to be sent","c":"sending","d":"to be sending","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Passive voice: Ask + to be PP","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Kerry is considering _________ his garage ___.","a":"having, rebuild","b":"to have, rebuild","c":"having, to be rebuilt","d":"having, rebuilt","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Consider + Verb_ing \n- Consider + Object + To Verb \n- Have sth done ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"The chemist was proud of _________ the Nobel Prize.","a":"her son won","b":"she having won","c":"her son's winning","d":"her son's having won","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Proud of +Verb_ing\/Noun","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"How about the three of us ___ a walk down the street?","a":"take","b":"to take","c":"to be taking","d":"taking","answer":"1","explain":"\n- How about (if) + Subject + Verb: used to mention something that may happen, and ask what should be done if it does happe","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Excuse _________ without ___.","a":"me for coming in, asking","b":"my coming in, being asked","c":"my coming in, asking","d":"me to come in, being asked","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Excuse me for doing sth: used to say that you are sorry for doing something rude or embarrassing","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Such great leaders are ___.","a":"to respect","b":"respect","c":"to be respected","d":"to be respecting","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Be To verb: imply the purpose \n- Passive voice: be to be PP","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Traveling is ___, but we often feel ___ when we are back from travels.","a":"interested, tiring","b":"interesting, tired","c":"interested, tired","d":"interesting, tiring","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Interested\/tired... is a past participle. When used as an adjective it says how someone feels. \n- Interesting\/tiring...: is a present participle. When used as an adjective it describes the people or things that cause the feelings","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"}]}